Congratulations on making it to the end of this short course.
恭喜你完成了这个短期课程。
In summary, in this short course,
简而言之，在这个短期课程中，
you've learned about two key principles for prompting.
你学到了关于提示的两个关键原则。
Write clear and specific instructions,
写清晰、明确的指令，
and when it's appropriate,
在适当的时候，
give the model time to think.
给模型一些时间去“思考”。
You also learned about iterative prompt development and how
你还了解了迭代式提示开发以及如何
having a process to get to the prompt is right for your application is key.
拥有一个适合你应用程序的获取提示的过程是关键。
And we went through a few capabilities of
我们还介绍了一些
large language models that are useful for many applications,
对许多应用有用的大型语言模型的功能，
specifically summarizing, inferring, transforming, and expanding.
特别是总结、推断、转换和扩展。
And you also saw how to build a custom chatbot.
你还了解了如何构建一个定制的聊天机器人。
That was a lot that you learned in just one short course,
在这么短的课程中，你学到了很多，
and I hope you enjoyed going through these materials.
希望你喜欢学习这些材料。
We hope you'll come up with some ideas for
我们希望你能想出一些创意
applications that you can build yourself now.
你现在可以可是构建自己的应用程序。
And please go try this out and let us know what you come up with.
试试看，并告诉我们，你想出了什么。
No application is too small.
任何应用程序都不小。
It's fine to start with something that's kind of
从一些很小的，
a very small project with maybe a little bit of utility,
可能也没什么实用性的小项目开始，也是可以的，
or maybe it's not even useful at all.
甚至可能毫无用处，
It's just something fun.
只是一些有趣的项目。
Yeah. And I find playing with these models actually really fun.
是的。而且我发现玩这些模型真的很有趣。
So go play with it.
所以去玩吧。
Yeah, I agree. It's a good,
是的，我同意。这是一个很好的，
a good weekend activity, speaking from experience.
这是一个很好的周末活动，根据经验来说。
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
Um, and just, you know,
呃，还有，你知道，
please use the learnings from your first project to build a better second project,
请运用你从第一个项目中学到的知识来构建一个更好的第二个项目，
and you know, maybe even a better third project, so on.
你知道的，可能甚至是一个更好的第三个项目，等等。
That's kind of how I have kind of grown over time using these models myself as well.
这也是我在使用这些模型的过程中逐渐成长起来的方式。
Um, or if you have an idea for a bigger project already,
呃，如果你已经有了一个更大项目的想法，
just, just go for it.
那就去做吧。
Um, and you know, as a reminder,
呃，提醒一下，
um, these kind of large language models are a very powerful technology.
这类大型语言模型是非常强大的技术。
So it kind of goes without saying that we ask you to use them responsibly,
所以，不言而喻，我们要求你负责任地使用它们，
and please only build things that will have a positive impact.
请只构建那些会产生积极影响的东西。
Yeah, fully agree. I think in this age,
是的，完全同意。我认为在这个时代，
people that build AI systems can have a huge impact on others.
构建AI系统的人对他人会产生巨大影响。
So it's more important than ever that all of us only use these tools responsibly.
因此，我们所有人都要负责任地使用这些工具，这一点比以往任何时候都更为重要。
Um, and I think building large language model-based applications
呃，我认为构建基于大型语言模型的应用程序
is just a very exciting and growing field right now.
现在是一个非常令人兴奋且不断发展的领域。
And now that you've finished this course,
既然你已经完成了这门课程，
I think you now have a wealth of knowledge that
我认为你现在已经拥有了丰富的知识，
let you build things that few people today know how to.
让你能够构建那些只有少数人知道如何构建的东西
So I hope you also help us to spread the word and encourage others to take this course too
与此同时，我希望你也能帮助我们传播信息，鼓励其他人也参加这个课程
In closing, I hope you had fun doing this course
最后，我希望你在做这个课程时很开心
and I want to thank you for finishing this course
同时也感谢你能完成这个课程
and both Isa and I look forward to hearing about the amazing things that you've built
Isa和我都期待着听到你所建立的惊人的东西9